isms.com.my 2019-06-07

# Bulk SMS Malaysia Policy | SMS Marketing | Online SMS Solution | Send SMS

### **Privacy Policy Statement**

#### **Mobiweb Sdn. Bhd**

Mobiweb's has evolved since established 2007. Deploying the latest telecommunications technology and internet technology, our goal is to provide a one stop, total business solution for your company's business. Our service ranges from telecommunications, for e.g VoIP, bulk sms, sms marketing, discounted calls and IDD cards; to business management solutions, for e.g online inventory system, online CRM system,online POS system, online membership system and bulk emails.

#### **iSMS**

iSMS is developed by Mobiweb. Our sms marketing tool offers international sms service covering more than 700 mobile operator worldwide from peer to peer sms, streaming content services such as factory alerts, news alerts and stock updates; bulk sms communications are based on high quality as well as reliable connectivity.

#### **Client Privacy and Data Security With iSMS**

Client's rights to both privacy and security is a major concern issue. Below are the guidelines that we use to protect your personal information. Please read the following statements carefully before proceeding.

#### **iSMS Respects Your Privacy**

In able to provide the services to our clients, we, iSMS will only collect, store and use your personal information for specific purposes. We _only_ use your personal information to support and enhance our relationship with you, and for other legitimate reasons described by the law. Your personal information is ensured by us, for we do not disclose, or sell your information; we only share your personal information outside iSMS with your consent, as required by the law or with companies that help iSMS to fulfill it's obligations with you, and only with partners who share iSMS's commitment in protecting your privacy and personal information or data. Clients are welcome to give us, iSMS's call center with any questions or concerns regarding your privacy and data security or request, as appropriate in making a correction or deletion. Our goal is to ensure the highest level of security and confidentiality for our client's personal information.

#### **The Information iSMS Collects About You**

iSMS only collect personal information which are necessary from our clients. By providing efficient and complete information about you enable us to process your request and provide services needed to you. This will also help us to enhance your site visit, respond to requests for information, support our client relationship, and enable to assist you with technical support issues and to follow up with you after your visit.

When iSMS is able to collect your personal information from you:

  * When you register on any domain name(s) and/ or website(s) that are registered to or on behalf of the company from time to time.
  * When you request a proposal for products and/ or services
  * Whenever you place an order for products and/ or services
  * When filling out a support request or requesting telephone technical support services
  * Provide feedback in an online survey
  * Participating in promotional offers
  * When subscribing to a newsletter or a mailing services

In each of the instances above, we may ask for your full name, current address, contact number, occupation, industry, transactional information and such as your preferences, customer number, credit card information and other bank details, referrals, and other information that is needed to process your purchase, requested services or to register you or to subscribe you to services and offers.

#### **iSMS Only Uses Your Personal Information in these Conditions:**

  * To process your purchase or providing requested services from you
  * To fulfill requests for products and services
  * To improve our products and services via feedback: and to contact you 
  * Newsletters, mailing lists, requests for more information

The information that you provide to us will be kept confidentially and is collected and processed for the general purposes and legitimate purposes described by the applicable law.

If you make a request from us, or any other iSMS entity or any other agent working on behalf of iSMS entities, we will send you information about our various services, product information and services that may be of interest to you. Such information may encompass alerts to upgrades, special offers, updated information and new products and services from iSMS. Only iSMS or agents working on behalf of iSMS are eligible to send you these mailings and information. But if you do not want to receive such mailings or information any longer, please kindly notify us by contacting us. 

#### **Circumstances that iSMS will Share Your Personal Information**

Your personal information may only shared with other iSMS entities, agents or contractors who perform services for iSMS, such as **Mobiweb Sdn. Bhd**. If so, iSMS will seek to ensure that the information is only used in connection with the functions that these parties will be performing for iSMS and that all such information is treated in a confidential and discreet manner.

iSMS will only **disclose** your personal information to the extent required or authorized by applicable law, or if ordered and required to do so by court or governmental authorities as appropriate in each jurisdiction, or to ensure that we are in compliance with our legal obligations.

iSMS will **not** **disclose** your personal information to any outsiders or other organizations for it's use in marketing. Personal information regarding about our clients (such as full name, current address and contact number), your order and products that you have purchased from us will not be given or sold to any other organizations for it's use in marketing or solicitation.

#### **Client's Rights**

Upon the request and within 30 days we will inform you about the type of personal information that we hold about you, the purposes and reasons for which we hold it and the possible recipients or types of recipients. Upon written request and within a reasonable period of time we will also correct, delete and/ or block personal information from further processing if that information proves to be factually inaccurate, incomplete, or irrelevant to the purpose(s) of the process.

#### **Third-Party Sites**

Please be aware that other websites including sites that may be accessed through our site, e.g., via a hyperlink, may collect personally identifiable information about you. This PRIVACY POLICY statement **does not** cover the information practices of those third- party websites linked to any of our websites or any other sites.

#### **Online Threats**

  * The information are used for some online applications, but every request to access and/ or change those copies is both logged and reviewed by our iSMS staffs. 
  * Our software applications are written to not be vulnerable to standard hacks like SQL injection.
  * Access to personal information (e.g information about individuals) requires at least a user ID and a password.
  * It is not technologically possible to absolutely guarantee the security of data stored in a computer.

Our goal is to make unauthorized or malicious access both difficult and detectable.

#### **If you have more question regarding the privacy policy statements please call us at:**

|   | 

Penang, Malaysia

| 

Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia  
  
---|---|---  
  
Call us 

| 

+604 642 0621

| 

+603 2780 3880  
  
Fax us

| 

+604 611 5620

| 

+603 7980 2388  
  
Email us

| 

sales@mobiweb.com.my

| 

sales@mobiweb.com.my  
  
Write to us

| 

Unit 1-3-31, i-Avenue,  
No. 1, Jalan Tun Dr Awang, 11900 Bayan Lepas, Penang, Malaysia

| 

No.B-2-7, Block B, Kuchai Exchange,  
Jalan Kuchai Maju 13, Kuchai Lama 58200,   
Kuala Lumpur, Malaysia
